Guide to the David Richmond Gergen Papers, 1964-1999 (bulk 1971-1992) RL.00443
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2000-0356)
  - Subject Files,1974-1976 (Box 78)
    - Agriculture (Box 78)
    - A Responsible Economic Package (Box 78)
    - Ford Speeches 1976 (Box 78)
    - Federal Budget, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Press Conferences (Box 78)
    - Capital Formation (Box 78)
    - Business Today (Box 78)
    - Business ethics (Box 78)
    - ABA and SIA Recommendation (Box 78)
    - Pierre Rinfret (Box 78)
    - Irving Kristol (Box 78)
    - C. Jackson Grayson (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous/loose papers (Box 78)
  - Three-dimensional items (Box 78)
    - Paperweight-Albion College, Gerald R. Ford Institute for Public Service (Box 78)
    - Paperweight-Carleton College (Box 78)
  - Personal Files; Notebook--1971 Agency Achievements; Notes from Bennett and Juilwon Meetings, [1974 July, 1975 January-1975 August] (Box 79)
    - American University Commencement 1975 May 18 (Box 79)
    - Background--American Univ. Commencement 1975 May 18 (Box 79)
    - Conference Board 1975 May 15 (Box 79)
    - Background--Conference Board 1975 May 15 (Box 79)
    - American Retail Federation 1975 May 15 (Box 79)
    - Background--American Retail Fed 1975 May 15 (Box 79)
    - Subcommittee--Commerce, Consumer and Mon 1974 May 14 (Box 79)
    - US-European Seminar, Atlantic Council 1975 May 13 (Box 79)
    - Background--US-European Seminar, 1975 May 13 (Box 79)
    - Business Council, Homestead 1975 May 8 (Box 79)
    - Background--Business Council, Homestead 1975 May 8 (Box 79)
    - Background--Business Council, Homestead 1975 May 9 (Box 79)
    - Toronto Society of Financial Analysts 1975 May 9 (Box 79)
    - Address by Secretary of the Treasury, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Testimony--Senate Finance Comm 1975 May 7, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Background--Toronto Society of Fin Analysts, 1975 May 8 (Box 79)
    - Crime in the U.S. 1975 April 28 (Box 79)
    - Talking Points--Simon Party (Awards) (Box 79)
    - Indo-US Chamber of Comm. (Bombay) 1975 April 18 (Box 79)
    - ADB--Manila Speech--1975 April 25 (Box 79)
    - HJC Hearings--Friday, 1974 July 16--Afternoon Session (Box 79)
    - Fall Campaign Registration (Box 79)
    - HJC Hearings--Friday, 1974 July 19--Executive Session (Box 79)
    - HJC Hearings--Saturday, 1974 July 27--Evening Session (Box 79)
    - HJC Hearings--Friday, 1974 July 19--Afternoon (Box 79)
    - Bkgd--Jr. Achievement 1975 August 12 (Box 79)
    - Jr. Achievement, Indiana 1975 August 12 (Box 79)
    - Miscellaneous 1972-1973 Memos, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Newspaper Article San Francisco Examiner (Box 79)
    - Newspaper Article Thimmisch Column (Box 79)
    - WES's TV Appearance-1975 January 19, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Brigham Young University1975 November 14, 3 folders (Box 80)
  - St. Louis Forum, St. Louis, Mo.1975 November 13 (Box 80)
  - Str. Byrd Testimonial, Richmond1975 November 13 (Box 80)
  - Joint Economic Cmte1975 November 7 (Box 80)
  - American Newspapers Publishers Asso. Chicago, Illinois1975 November 5 (Box 80)
  - Lincoln Forum, Salt Lake City1975 November 13 (Box 80)
  - Walker Lecture, U of Pittsburgh1975 November 5 (Box 80)
  - Diaries, 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Camp David--Background Material (Box 80)
  - Speeches, 7 folders (Box 80)
  - Cheney (Notes to and from) (Box 80)
  - Communications Group (Gergen) (Box 80)
  - Republican Platform (Box 80)
  - Auspitz, Lee (Box 80)
  - 1975 (Box 80)
  - Nixon (Box 80)
  - Public Polls, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Presidential Films, 3 folders (Box 81)
  - Polls, 4 folders (Box 81)
  - Discuss with Dick Cheney, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Chron File,1976 October, 3 folders (Box 81)
  - 1976 Presidential Election Analyses (Box 81)
  - [Loose materials] (Box 82)
    - [Articles concerningReagan] (Box 82)
    - [Articles concerningReagan administration] (Box 82)
    - [Newspaper articles/clippings,1977], 3 folders (Box 82)
    - [Big government], 2 folders (Box 82)
  - Watergate: notes (Box 82)
  - Illinois-Chicago (Box 82)
  - File information -1964 (Box 82)
  - Miscellaneous Memos (Box 82)
  - [Loose Material, Speech1976 January 10] (Box 82)
  - New York City Crisis, 2 folders (Box 82)
  - [Loose Material, Drafts of Speeches], 4 folders (Box 82)
  - Taxes, 4 folders (Box 83)
  - [Draft of Speech] (Box 83)
  - SOTU #4 [Draft of Speech] (Box 83)
  - Budget Message, 1976 January 9, 2 folders (Box 83)
  - Background--II's Tax Cut/Spending Speech (Box 83)
  - [Loose Material: Draft of Speech] (Box 83)
  - [Loose Material: Mainly Memos] (Box 83)
  - Memo from William Baroody Re: Campaign Themes (Box 83)
  - #10 Anthology of Anecdotes, 3rd Yr.; Report; Inaugural Mementos, incl. License plates; personal mail,1971-1973 (Box 83)
    - Daily Planner, 1973 (Box 83)
    - Daily Planner, 1974, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Inaugural License plate, 1973 and Republican National Convention license plate, 1972 (Box 83)
    - [Correspondence and Financial materials] (Box 83)
    - [RichardNixon Materials], 1971-1973 (Box 83)
    - Schedules (Box 83)
  - [continued material from box 81] (Box 84)
    - Purification and Translation of Globin MRNA1977 [this folder title may not reflect the material inside] (Box 84)
  - WES Speech File1975 May-1975 June (Box 84)
    - Indiana Broadcasters Association, 1975 June 6 (Box 84)
    - Newark Academy--Newark, NJ--1975 June 6, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - National Invest in America Council--1975 June 4, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Joint Economic Committee 1975 June 4 (Box 84)
    - NJ Sales Exec Club and Rutgers 3 1975 June, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Talk Points: Senior Seminar in Foreign Policy 1975 June 2 (Box 84)
    - American Advertising Federation--1975 June 2, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Economic Intelligence Weekly--Secret (Box 84)
    - News and Comment (Box 84)
    - News and Comment, 1976 (Box 93)
    - Bond Club--NYC--1975 May 30 (Box 84)
    - OECD [Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development] Speech--Paris--1975 May 29 (Box 84)
    - SC Bankers Association, Myrtle Beach, 1975 May 23, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Amer. Iron and Steel NY City, 1975 May 22 (Box 84)
    - Talking Points Reader's Digest 1975 May 22, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Santa Domingo Speech, 2 folders (Box 84)
  - Papers relating to Watergate, ITT, MILK, Taxes (Mostly background drafts, memos re: white papers on above) (Box 85)
    - Public Citizen, Inc. vs. Clawson (Box 85)
    - Dean vs. RN: Summary Memorandum (Box 85)
    - Watergate Chronology, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Watergate Speech 4-5 Drafts,1973 September (Box 85)
    - Chronology: Presidential meetings (Box 85)
    - Press Clippings--Watergate (Box 85)
    - Watergate Briefs and Briefings, 3 folders (Box 85)
    - Watergate White Paper1973 May and 1973 August (Box 85)
    - Watergate Memos (Box 85)
    - Watergate White Paper, 1973 August, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Watergate Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 85)
    - White Papers--ITT, Milk, Taxes, 3 folders (Box 85)
  - Subject files;1976 Debates; 1976 Convention (Box 86)
    - Nevada--Media, 6 folders (Box 86)
    - Debates, 3 folders (Box 86)
    - GOP Convention1976, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - New Jersey--Media, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - New Hampshire, 3 folders (Box 86)
  - Subject files;1976 Debates; 1976 Convention (Box 87)
    - Illinois (Box 87)
    - GOP Convention --TV Monitor (Box 87)
  - Subject files,1976-1976 (Box 87)
    - Newspaper Project (Working File) (Box 87)
    - American Jewish Committee Dinner- 1976 May 13 (Box 87)
    - Q & A, Campaign 1976 (Box 87)
    - Eastern Europe (Box 87)
    - Independence Hall (Box 87)
    - Jaycees Convention 1976 June 22 (Box 87)
    - Law Day Speech (drugs) (Box 87)
    - Mondale Speeches (Box 87)
    - National Security (DAR Speech bkgd) (Box 87)
    - Nebraska Commencement Address (Box 87)
    - News Summary (Box 87)
    - Polling (Box 87)
    - Presidential Scheduling (Box 87)
    - Presidential Speeches (Box 87)
    - Regulatory Reform (Box 87)
    - Rubenstein, Arthur, 2 color photos (Box 87)
    - Stump Speech (Box 87)
    - TV Appeal (Box 87)
    - Texas Speech (Box 87)
    - Questions and Answers (Box 87)
    - Q & A DĂŠtente (Box 87)
    - Q & A Presidency (Box 87)
    - Q & A Republican Party (Box 87)
    - Q & A Vice President (Box 87)
  - #13 Miscell. GD Memos,1974; Misc. Remarks Prepared for RN-1973-1974; December Group Notes; Daily WG Calendar; Misc. WG Defense Papers (Box 88)
    - Watergate-Miscellaneous
      - Miscellaneous Remarks Prepared for RN,1973 (Box 88)
      - Some DG Memos,1974, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - December Group-Decision Summary,1972 (Box 88)
    - Milk White Paper, 4 folders (Box 88)
    - Federal Council on the Arts and Humanities (Box 88)
    - 1974 Remarks, Other Material, 3 folders (Box 88)
    - Watergate Calendars (Box 88)
  - Plaques/awards and pictures (Box 89)
    - Presented to David Gergen by the American Watch Association,1997 May 14 (Box 89)
    - Color picture in frame of Gergen with a group of people (Box 89)
    - Air Force Association Special Award to David Gergen for his column Saluting those who serve, 1997 (Box 89)
  - Three-dimensional items (Box 89)
    - Statue-Washington, DC Capitol Building (Box 89)
  - Plaques/awards (Box 90)
    - 1981 Republican Senate House Dinner Thanks for making it Great! (Box 90)
      [note includes signatures of Bob Packwood, Guy VanderJagt, and Joe M. Rodgers]
    - In Recognition as Keynote Speaker for the Third Annual North Carolina Support Our Students Conference,1997 March 3 (Box 90)
    - Certificate of Appreciation in recognition of address before the McLean Business and Professional Association,1987 March 17 (Box 90)
  - Decorated binders and other artwork (Box 91)
  - Plastic Identification Card,Reagan andBush Committee,1980 August 28 (Box 91)
  - Book of matches-Vice President's House (Box 91)
  - Spokesman Inventory,1976 May 5 (Box 92)
    [computer printouts]
  - The Bicentennial Speeches of President Gerald R. Ford,1976 July 1-1976 July 5 (Box 92)
    [from box 60]
  - Citation to David Gergen, Appointed to the Committee on Communications of the Republican National Committee,1978-1979 (Box 92)
  - Color photographs of PresidentNixon (Box 92)
    [from box 61]
- Accession (2000-0415)
  This collection is RESTRICTED: Researchers must obtain Gergen's permission before using any part of this collection. In addition, the collection contains sensitive material throughout, including public records.
  - SR 18 (Box 1)
    - AEI (Box 1)
    - American Committee on US-Soviet Relations (Box 1)
    - American Political Report (Box 1)
    - Bradley's New West (Box 1)
    - The Brookings Inst (Box 1)
    - Busby (Box 1)
    - Congressional Quarterly (Box 1)
    - Cook Political Report (Box 1)
    - Defense Monitor (Box 1)
    - Dispatch - US Dept of State (Box 1)
    - Eastern Europe Travel (Box 1)
    - Eastern Europe Trip (Box 1)
    - Economic Policy Inst - Briefing Papers (Box 1)
    - Economic Strategy Inst (Box 1)
    - Evans Novak (Box 1)
    - Foreign Report (Box 1)
    - Governors Bulletin (Box 1)
    - Janeway (Box 1)
    - Kiplinger (Box 1)
    - Mayo Clinic Health Letter (Box 1)
    - Misc. Newsletters (Box 1)
    - M/L - Responses to, 4 folders (Box 1)
    - Points West, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - PPI (Box 1)
    - Resumes, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - RJR Nabisco (Box 1)
    - U.N. Observer (Box 1)
    - Unger, Sanford (Box 1)
    - Vance, Cyrus (Box 1)
    - Weidenfeld, Prof, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Weinberger (Box 1)
    - Wellstone, Sen. Paul (Box 1)
    - Westin (Box 1)
    - Warton, Dolores (Box 1)
    - Willett, Sandra (Box 1)
    - Wirth, Sen. Timothy (Box 1)
    - Wischard, Van (Box 1)
    - Wolf, Rep. Frank, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Wright, Jim (Box 1)
    - Yamamoto, Tadashi (Box 1)
    - Yardini (Box 1)
    - Yeltsin (Box 1)
    - Yew, Lee Kuan (Box 1)
    - Zoellick, Bob (Box 1)
  - SR 18, continued (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - SR 7 (Box 2)
    - Daily Phone logs,1988-1991 (Chronological by months and years) (Box 2)
  - SR 44- Editorials-Source Files1990-1991; WMAL Commentaries1989-1992 (Box 3)
    - Source: Crime Edit. (Box 3)
    - DG Editorial; 1991 September 9; America's Best Export (Box 3)
    - DG Editorial; 1991 November 11; Let's Get Real (Box 3)
    - Exec. Brkst. Club, 1991 October 18 (Box 3)
    - 1991 July 8>Bush, NWO> TMW (Box 3)
    - DG Commentary; 1991 October 21; Germany (Box 3)
    - DG WMAL Commentary; 1991 July 8; Housing (Box 3)
    - DG Editorials; 1991 August 19; America's Legal Mess (Box 3)
    - June 24 TMW>Bush '1992 (Box 3)
    - Housing Edit: 1991 July 22 (Box 3)
    - DG Commentary;, 1991 September 2; Lawyers--commentary II (Legal Mess) (Box 3)
    - Moynihan (Box 3)
    - CEO Int'l. Magazine (Box 3)
    - Culture Gap, Aramony (Box 3)
    - One Week; 1992 March 2; Western Elections (Box 3)
    - Heroes for Hire; 1992 January 27; editorial (writing material) (Box 3)
    - DG Editorial; 1991 October 7, 1991;Death on Doorsteps (Box 3)
    - DG Commentary; 1991 October 28; Reform/Fix the Confirm. Process, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - DG Editorial; 1991 October 14; Profiles on Privilege (Box 3)
    - Bush/Media: 1992 January 13 (Box 3)
    - Media/Recession: 1992 January 13 (Box 3)
    - October 5 Perot 5 Edit (Box 3)
    - Source--DG Edit; 1991 July 15; Judge Clarence Thomas, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Family Leave 1992 September 28 (Box 3)
    - WMAL 6:30 on 630 TRW, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - [Loose Material: Commentaries], 3 folders (Box 3)
  - SR 33- Gergen Info. Files [S?-Y] (Box 4)
    - Smithsonian Institution Thomas Jefferson Commemoration (Box 4)
    - Tomorrow (Box 4)
    - [Trialog 44] Lisbon1992, The annual Meeting of the Trilateral Commission (Box 4)
    - Trilateral Commiss. (Box 4)
    - 1992 Annual Financial Report, University of Maryland at College Park (Box 4)
    - University of Maryland School of Public Affairs Board of Visitors Meeting1992 May 19 (Box 4)
    - A Survey of American Attitudes toward Health Care Reform, Tabular Report #1,1993 March (Box 4)
    - Urban Public Policy (Box 4)
    - Urban Issues/Problems (Box 4)
    - Urban Violence (Box 4)
    - U.S. Govt.--Loan Guarantee (Box 4)
    - U.S. News (Box 4)
    - Utilities (Box 4)
    - Value-added Tax (Box 4)
    - Very Special Arts (Box 4)
    - Voter Turnout/Dems. in June (Box 4)
    - Voting (Box 4)
    - Wash. Campus Info. (Box 4)
    - The Washington Campus--correspondence (Box 4)
    - Water (Box 4)
    - Watergate (Box 4)
    - Ways and Means Comm (Box 4)
    - Weekend Shows--Trascrts (Box 4)
    - Welfare (Box 4)
    - Wilton Park, Perot (Box 4)
    - WMAL, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Women in Media (Box 4)
    - Women/ Politics (Box 4)
    - World Economic Forum (Box 4)
    - The World Competitiveness Report, 1991 (Box 4)
    - World Economic Forum Annual Meeting, Highlights and Summary of the Programme,1991 (Box 4)
    - World Economic Forum Annual Meeting, Highlights and Summary of the Programme,1992 (Box 4)
    - World Economic Forum,1993 Annual Meeting, January Update (Box 4)
    - World Link (Box 4)
    - The World and I (Box 4)
    - Yugoslavia (Box 4)
    - Rebuilding America's Cities Together draft (Box 4)
  - SR 15- Int'l Files 3rd Floor (Box 5)
    - Gannett Foundation Media Center (Box 5)
    - Germany (Box 5)
    - Education, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - El Salvador (Box 5)
    - US Environment Issues, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - European Economic Comm., EEC (Box 5)
    - Fast Track--Congress (Box 5)
    - Foreign Trade (Box 5)
    - France (Box 5)
    - The Freedom Forum Media Studies Center (Box 5)
    - French-American Foundation (Box 5)
    - Gulf War, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Congress/Gulf War (Box 5)
    - Guinea (Box 5)
    - US--Health Care (Box 5)
    - Health Care:Bush/Cong. '1992 (Box 5)
    - Hoover Institution (Box 5)
    - Hudson Institute (Box 5)
    - InterAction Council (Box 5)
    - International Affairs (Box 5)
    - Int'l Broadcasting Task Force (Box 5)
    - International Economics, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - International Media Relations (Box 5)
    - Investments--US/Foreign (Box 5)
    - Israel (Box 5)
    - Israeli Economy (Box 5)
  - SR 15-Int'l Files 3rd Floor, continued (Box 6)
    - Japan, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Japan-American Assembly (Box 6)
    - Jacques Delors' speech--president of European Commission, London,1991 March 7 (Box 6)
    - Reading Material cont. (Box 6)
    - Comments & Papers: from Colleagues, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - SR 25 Info. Files, CSIS mostly (Box 6)
    - Crime (see source: Crime edit file) (Box 6)
    - Defense Bill (Box 6)
    - Defense (Box 6)
    - CSIS: Strengthening of America (Box 6)
    - The US Air Force Report to the 102nd Congress (Box 6)
    - Decline--US (Box 6)
    - Duke: Board Policy (Box 6)
    - Duke: Dept. of Math. (Box 6)
    - Drugs (Box 6)
    - Debates '1992 (Box 6)
    - Diebold Group (Box 6)
    - Ditchley Foundation (Box 6)
    - Divided Government (Box 6)
    - CSIS: Strengthening of America, Fri, March 1, Rayburn Bldg., 2237, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - SR 25, continued (Box 7)
    - DG Publications, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - DG Quotes1992 July-1992 November (Box 7)
    - Democratic Convention (Box 7)
    - DG Mailing List (Box 7)
    - Defense Secretaries, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Democracy (Box 7)
    - Democrats:1992 Agenda (Box 7)
    - 1992 Democratic Pres. Race (Box 7)
    - DG: Magazine Articles: Index (Box 7)
    - Defense Spending (Box 7)
    - Democracy (Box 7)
  - SR 30 [and continued in box 15] (Box 7)
    - Election1988:
      - Nixon Sunday Times of London 1988 November 3 (Box 7)
      - After the Election....1988 (Box 7)
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - The Washington Campus (Box 7)
    - Health Care:
      - Cat. Health Care (Box 7)
      - 25 Edit Source File (Box 7)
      - Health Care Clips (Box 7)
    - Ethics:
      - Ethics: Center for Ex. in Gov't. (Box 7)
      - Media Ethics (Box 7)
      - Ethics Clips (Box 7)
    - Defense:
      - [Unfoldered material: UTC Jupiter Island, Fla.1989 March] (Box 7)
      - UTC Jupiter Island, Fla.1989 March (Box 7)
    - DC:
      - Recycle (Box 7)
    - Congress:
      - [Loose Material: Federal Salaries report] (Box 7)
      - Greenbriar1989/Democrats Annual Visit (Box 7)
    - Center for Excellence in Govt (Box 7)
    - Election1988 II:
      - Polls (Box 7)
      - Savings (Box 7)
      - AFSCME'S election1988survey (Box 7)
      - NBC News Decision1988 General Election Poll Results (Box 7)
      - Report: Council on Competitiveness1988 (Box 7)
    - Democrats in1989:
      - Gov. Cuomo (Box 7)
    - Drugs, files were in 2 hanging folders):
      - Drug Czar Bennett (Box 7)
      - Drugs (Box 7)
      - War on Drugs (Box 7)
    - Hanging folder 2:
      - [Loose material: from Network for Public Debate] (Box 7)
      - National Issues Forums:The Drug Crisis (Box 7)
    - [Untitled accordion file: Aspen Institute Speech] (Box 7)
    - Environment, 1 and 2 of 3 folders--files continue in Box 16 (Box 7)
  - SR 39 (Box 8)
    - Racism (Box 8)
    - RAND (Box 8)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Africa Material, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - SAIS - Book Project (Box 8)
    - US/Soviet Union - Defense Strategies (Box 8)
    - Soviet - US Relations (Box 8)
    - The Stanley Foundation (Box 8)
    - Taxes (Box 8)
    - US- Taxes - Policies/Problems (Box 8)
    - Taxes: Value-Added (Box 8)
    - Technology (Box 8)
    - Technology: Computer (Box 8)
    - Technology, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Telecommunications (Box 8)
    - Television Shows (Box 8)
    - Think Mag (Box 8)
    - Tiananmen Square, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Thank You Notes -1990 September-1991 December, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Trade (Box 8)
    - United Nations (Box 8)
    - Urban Problems (Box 8)
    - USIA - Treasury Panel (Box 8)
    - US Policy (Box 8)
    - US Role in the World (Box 8)
    - Vice Presidents (Box 8)
    - War Games, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - SR 39, continued (Box 9)
    - Worldwatch Paper, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - World Economic Forum - DAVOS (Box 9)
    - Trilateral Commission Mtgs. (Box 9)
    - Earth Summit - Media Briefing,1992 (Box 9)
    - Secretaries of Defense,1992, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Secretary of State Conference,1992 (Box 9)
  - SR 38, D. Gergen1991 May 15,1989-1990 [continued in box 12] (Box 9)
    - Printed Material (Box 9)
    - John J. Gergen Memorial Fund (Box 9)
    - China, 4 folders (Box 9)
    - NATO/US-Germany-USSR, 6 folders, but the 6th folder is in box 12 (Box 9)
  - Clinton Administration (Box 10)
    - NAFTA, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - UN, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Vietnam, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Rwanda (Box 10)
    - Middle East, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Japan (Box 10)
    - Defense, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Duke University (Box 10)
    - Reagan, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Fall Priorities (Box 10)
    - Fall Calendar (Box 10)
    - Legislative Agenda (Box 10)
    - Speeches, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Articles/Readings (Box 10)
    - Cabinet: Cross-Party Lines (Box 10)
    - The Press: Decline in Civility (Box 10)
    - External Writings (Pre-W.H.) (Box 10)
    - Correspondence - Personal Notes, Friends, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Tony Lake (Box 10)
    - Democratic Leadership (Box 10)
    - From, Al, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Jokes (Box 10)
    - Mack McLarty, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Kleinberg, Susan (Box 10)
    - Kerrey, Sen. Bob (Box 10)
    - Morris, Dick (Box 10)
    - Joe Fleishman (Box 10)
    - Christopher Gergen (Box 10)
    - Photos (Box 10)
    - Moynihan, Sen. (Box 10)
  - Clinton Administration, continued (Box 11)
    - Steve Gergen (Box 11)
    - Kathleen Hall Jamieson/ Annenberg Carter (Box 11)
    - The Bohemian Club (photo) (Box 11)
    - Incoming Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Photos (Box 11)
    - Personal Notes, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Incoming Correspondence,1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Briefing Material - Europe Trip (Box 11)
    - Personal Notes (Box 11)
    - Book Material (Box 11)
    - Personnel (Box 11)
    - Security Forms (Box 11)
    - Chron. File, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Nixon (Box 11)
    - Nixon Funeral (Box 11)
    - Notebooks and Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - [end of] SR 14 from box 18 (Box 11)
    - [Small Business] (Box 11)
    - National Service (Box 11)
  - SR38, continued from box 9 (Box 12)
    - NATO/US-Germany-USSR (6th folder continued from box 9) (Box 12)
    - NATO-II, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - SR 31 (Box 12)
    - Moderator's Briefing Book, Conference at the White House, Economies in Transition,1991, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - People1989, 5 folders (Box 12)
      (includes handwritten letter fromNixon to Gergen in first folder and audio tape in 5th folder)
    - Hungary/ Peter Rajcsanyi (Box 12)
    - US Future, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - SR 31, continued [and continued in box 15] (Box 13)
    - Britain, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Abortion, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - People 1989, 4 folders (Box 13)
    - Americans Talk Security, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - US Economy/Savings (Box 13)
    - Media 1989 (Box 13)
      (includes photograph of Gergen on Face the Nation)
    - Inter American Dialogue (Box 13)
  - SR 20-Editorial Contents, 3rd Floor (Box 13)
    - Aspen Institute, Summer1991, 8 folders (Box 13)
      Includes papers Gergen wrote and materials from the Strategy Group Foreign Affairs
    - article,1992, 4 folders (Box 13)
  - SR 20, continued (Box 14)
    - 1993 February 5: Health Care, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Editorials and speeches written and given by Gergen,1992-1993, 9 folders (Box 14)
    - Inaugural Notebook (Box 14)
    - [Environment/Policy] (Box 14)
    - [Printed Material] (Box 14)
    - [G7 Council]1993 (Box 14)
    - Ken's [Gergen] Book Party (Box 14)
    - Financial materials, 35 folders (Box 14)
      Including expenses and income, and speaker contract with Cosby
    - Personal chron file,1990 June-1990 November (Box 14)
  - SR 21-D. Gergen1991 May 15 (Box 14)